{
  "BASIC_MATH": [
    {
      "question": "1 &#43; 1",
      "answer": 2,
      "choices": [11, 1, 2, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "100 &#43; 0",
      "answer": 100,
      "choices": [10, 1000, 101, 100]
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &#8722; 1",
      "answer": 9,
      "choices": [10, 9, 11, 101]
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &#215; 4",
      "answer": 28,
      "choices": [28, 32, 47, 74]
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &#247; 2",
      "answer": 4,
      "choices": [4, 82, 8, 3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Tom has 3 apples. Andy has 2 apples. Melissa ate one of Tom's apple. How many apples do Tom and Andy have all together?",
      "answer": 4,
      "choices": [4, 2, 1, 5]
    }
  ],
  "PRE_ALGEBRA": [
    {
      "question": "&radic;4",
      "answer": 2,
      "choices": [2, 1, 16, 4]
    },
    {
      "question": "2<sup>3</sup>",
      "answer": 8,
      "choices": [16, 4, 8, 9]
    },
    {
      "question": "9<sup>1</sup>",
      "answer": 9,
      "choices": [9, 18, 1, 81]
    },
    {
      "question": "2<sup>-1</sup>",
      "answer": "<sup>1</sup>&frasl;<sub>2</sub>",
      "choices": [
        "<sup>1</sup>&frasl;<sub>4</sub>",
        "2",
        "<sup>1</sup>&frasl;<sub>8</sub>",
        "<sup>1</sup>&frasl;<sub>2</sub>"]
    }
  ],
  "GEOMETRY": [
  ],
  "ALGEBRA": [
  ]
}